<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF Paris</title>
    <link>http://wwwcncfparis.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CNCF Paris</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 14:41:29 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://wwwcncfparis.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>À propos</title>
      <link>http://wwwcncfparis.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 14:41:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wwwcncfparis.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Cloud Native Computing Paris est une association Loi 1901 visant à promouvoir les technologies Cloud Native. Le Cloud Native Computing permet de déployer des applications dans un environnement élastique et résilient.
Les technologies utilisées permettent l&#39;orchestration de containers Linux dans un écosystème distribué. Ce groupe permet de partager nos expériences respectives autour de ces récentes solutions et concepts. Nous aborderons des sujets aussi divers que la virtualisation réseau, les meilleures pratiques de développement ainsi que toutes les solutions de &amp;ldquo;microservices&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jobteaser Development Environments &amp; Monitoring Cloud Native Apps</title>
      <link>http://wwwcncfparis.github.io/posts/jobteaser-development-environments-monitoring-cloud-native-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 23:57:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wwwcncfparis.github.io/posts/jobteaser-development-environments-monitoring-cloud-native-apps/</guid>
      <description>Hi folks!
Our next event will be hosted by Jobteaser. Warm thanks to them :)
JobTeaser is a French company that provides recruitment solutions to companies for the recruitment of young talent and a free career center software to higher education institutions in Europe.
Serving 2.5 million students and recent graduates; 70,000 businesses; and a network of 600 higher education institutions in 19 European countries, JobTeaser is now the European leader for the recruitment of young talent in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>